Riccardo Fusiello

About me

Hi, I'm Riccardo Fusiello, I'm an ex student of the ITIS Sen.Onofrio Jannuzzi in Andria. I completed the five years of the ITIS in 2021 with a lot of great grades, particularly in the main subjects. Actually I'm studying Computer Science at University of Trento and my inspiration is to work in a great company of Computer Science or generally in a great company that invests in Computer Science and Innovation.

Personal Website: https://riccardofus.github.io/Cavi-Website/

Email: fusyriccardo@gmail.com **Phone**: (+39) 3895398639 **Date of birth**: 25/11/2002

Address: Via Pericle 120, 76123 Andria (Italia)

Working Experience

 $13/03/2023 - \dots$ IT Service Desk at University of Trento 01/03/2022 - 15/03/2022 Full Stack Developer at Reply S.p.A, Remote 15/06/2020 - 15/09/2020 Full Stack Developer at Nuvité S.r.l, Andria 22/05/2019 - 07/06/2019 Vocational Training at Exprivia S.p.A, Molfetta

Education

 $17/09/2021 - \dots$ Computer Science Student at University of Trento 15/09/2016 - 15/06/2021 Diploma in IT at ITIS Sen. Onofrio Jannuzzi, Andria (100L/100) 15/09/2019 - 21/06/2020 Certification on CCNA Routing and Switching: Introduction to Network of Cisco 15/01/2021 - 04/06/2021 Certification on Use and Programming of Comau Academy

Languages

Italian Mothertongue English B1/B2, spoken every day and used to write sometimes

Programming Languages that I know:

C/C++, Java, Python, JavaScript (React, Angular, NodeJS, ...), CSS, HTML, C#, Arduino, SQL, Shell

Autorizzo il trattamento dei miei dati personali, ai sensi del D. lgs. 196 del 30 giugno 2003